



Russian citizen Feb 3rd, 1994

CONTACT

+ 79657224760

amr99mohammed99@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/Amr99Mohammed99

https://portfolio-amr99mohammed99.netlify.app



Tver - Russia

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

Russian

PUBLICATIONS

Amr Khalil Saeed Thabit Mohammed, Svetlana Fedorovna Fedulova "Analysis of the economy and state budget of Yemen in the context of the civil war and political contradictions" FSBEI HE "Udmurt State University" 2019, page 158-163.

Budget as a subject of social sciences: collection of articles of the international scientific-practical conference (17-18 Oct. 2019).

About me

I'm a Junior Frontend Developer with an engineering background. I am dedicated to finding solutions and explanations for the challenges that arise for both my clients and myself. My dedication to solving challenges is matched by strong communication skills, honed through my university education and professional experience. I excel at understanding client needs, ensuring their satisfaction, and continually improving my technical abilities through self-study in frontend development.

Experiences

Sumsub (Sum and Substance Ltd) | Nov 2021 To Dec 2024 **Quality Control Operator, Russia**

- Maintained accurate quality documentation in regulatory compliance
- Analyze and correct graphical and numerical data arrays
- Control the quality of work of automated analysis systems
- Fill out applications in English, Arabic and Russian
- Executed quality control procedures aligned with the regulatory standards

Yandex Crowd | Sep 2023 To Nov 2023

Data Markup Specialist (with knowledge of Arabic), Russia

- Correction and debugging of Alice device conversations
- Analyze and processing of voice input of speakers to Alice
- Guide Alice to the correct scenarios to develop the efficiency of understanding the speaker's speech and the task required successfully

IPTV (Internet Protocol television) - NSZX | Jan 2020 To Nov 2021 Customer Support Specialist & Sales Specialist (B2B & B2C), Egypt

- Reception and verification of requests for undergoing the procedure
- Verification of the application and documents in Arabic and English
- Coordinate and fill out applications and carefully fill in the data
- Processing inquiries, e-mails, and contacts clients
- Analysis and problem solving
- Promoting subscription packages and their features to customers
- Made sales of IPTV services & devices to both companies and consumers in the B2B and B2C sectors

Education

Master's Degree: Financial Risk Management | 2018 To 2020 Udmurt State University, Izhevsk - Russia

Bachelor's Degree: Technical Maintenance of Aircrafts and Aircraft Engines | 2013 To 2018

University of Kazan National Research Technical named after A. N. Tupolev, Kazan - Russia

Programming Projects

- Create 50 JS Apps Elzero Acadamy | Present time
- Craft Professional WP Theme Elzero Acadamy | Present time

HOBBIES

Traveling Photograph

Socializing Gaming

PROGRAMS

- Html
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Git & GitHub
- GitHub Desktop
- Visual Studio Code
- Cmder
- Scratch
- Netlify
- Mattermost
- CondorSoft Dashboard
- Microsoft Office
- Microsoft Team
- Google Documents
- Adobe Lightroom
- Adobe Photoshop
- Slack
- Xmind
- Canva
- Notion

Personal Qualities

- Proficient in creating responsive and user-friendly interfaces
- Ability to effectively collaborate with clients and stakeholders to meet project requirements
- Strong attention to detail, ensuring clean and efficient code
- Capable of debugging and solving complex coding issues under pressure
- Excellent teamwork and collaboration skills in agile development environments
- Dedicated to writing maintainable, scalable, and high-quality code
- Passionate about learning new frontend technologies and improving programming skills

Courses

Responsive Web Design (Specialization) - Scrimba | Dec 2024

Build a Responsive Layout with CSS Grid - Scrimba | Dec 2024

Build a Hometown Homepage with HTML and CSS - Scrimba | Dec 2024

Build a product splash page with HTML and CSS - Scrimba | Dec 2024

Build a Responsive Website with HTML and CSS - Scrimba | Dec 2024

Learn CSS Animations - Scrimba | Dec 2024

Introduction to CSS3 - University of Michigan | Dec 2024

Learn Bootstrap - Scrimba | Nov 2024

Computer Hardware Basics - CISCO | Nov 2024

Using Computer and Mobile Devices - CISCO | Nov 2024

How To Create a Website in a Weekend! (Project-Centered Course) - The

State University of New York | Nov 2024

Programming Foundations with JavaScript, HTML and CSS - Duke

University | Nov 2024

Learn CSS Variables - Scrimba | Nov 2024

Learn CSS Grid - Scrimba | Nov 2024

Learn CSS Flexbox - Scrimba | Nov 2024

Learn HTML and CSS - Scrimba | Oct 2024

Introduction to HTML5 - University of Michigan | Aug 2023

HTML - Front-End Developer - LearnQuest | Jul 2023

Raster graphics. Adobe Photoshop CC - Peter the Great St. Petersburg

Polytechnic University | Apr 2020

English Course - Advanced - English Castle | Jan 2021

Concepts & Dealing with Electronic Spreadsheets - Specto | Apr 2020

Professional Excel Series - Rwak Platform | Nov 2018

Fundamentals of Graphic Design - California Institute of the | May 2018

English for Career Development - University of Pennsylvania | Dec 2017

English Access Microscholarship Program - Amideast/Yemen | Aug 2012